Finding aid to the Granddaughters' Society records CA.MS.00092
Smith College Archives
Granddaughters' Society records
1904-1966
Smith College Archives
Granddaughters' Society
CA.MS.00092
0.417 linear feet (1 container)
The Granddaughters' Society was an organization comprised of Smith students whose mothers attended Smith, thus making them "granddaughters" of the college itself. This collection includes mainly photographs and newspaper clippings concerning the activities and membership of the Granddaughters' Society.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Source unknown
Biographical / Historical
The Granddaughters' Society was an organization comprised of Smith students whose mothers attended Smith, thus making them "granddaughters" of the college itself.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes mainly photographs and newspaper clippings concerning the activities and membership of the Granddaughters' Society.
Smith College--Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College--Societies, etc.
- General, 1904 (Box 3014)
- General, 1906 (Box 3014)
- General, 1907 (Box 3014)
- General, 1914 (Box 3014)
- General, 1917 (Box 3014)
- General, 1923 (Box 3014)
- General, 1924 (Box 3014)
- General, 1925 (Box 3014)
- General, 1926 (Box 3014)
- General, 1927 (Box 3014)
- General, 1928 (Box 3014)
- General, 1929 (Box 3014)
- General, 1931 (Box 3014)
- General, 1932 (Box 3014)
- General, 1933 (Box 3014)
- General, 1935 (Box 3014)
- General, 1936 (Box 3014)
- General, 1937 (Box 3014)
- General, 1938 (Box 3014)
- General, 1939 (Box 3014)
- General, 1940 (Box 3014)
- General, 1942 (Box 3014)
- General, 1955 (Box 3014)
- General, 1956 (Box 3014)
- General, 1957 (Box 3014)
- General, 1960-1965 (Box 3014)
- General, 1966 (Box 3014)
- Photographs, 1904-1930 (Box 3014)
- Photographs, 1931-1947; undated (Box 3014)